Ethel Hopkins papers, 1933-1954
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Ethel Hopkins papers, 1933-1954
MS 404
Ethel Hopkins
Papers, 1933-1954. This collection is composed of the papers of Ethel "Ma" Hopkins. The bulk of the material is correspondence relating to her position as editor and publisher of Hoofs and Horns Magazine. Also included are photographs and prints, mostly depicting rodeo characters, rodeo scenes, and Western ranch activities of the period.
9.75 Linear Feet (Approximately 12,800 items)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Ethel A. Hopkins was born and raised on a farm in Missouri. She graduated from the University of Missouri in 1908 and worked as a school teacher in both Missouri and Oklahoma. She came to Tucson in 1916 due to the ill health of her husband and continued to work, first as a school teacher and later as a stenographer and secretary at the University of Arizona. After the passing of her first husband she married J. W. Hopkins, an officer at the Acme Printing Company. In 1933 Mrs. Hopkins purchased Hoofs and Horns Magazine, a weekly cattle paper that had ceased publication during the depression. She re-conceptualized Hoofs and Horns, first publishing it in October of 1933 as a monthly magazine, shifting the focus towards the sport of rodeo while still accommodating the interests of cattlemen. Mrs. Hopkins acted as publisher and editor of Hoofs and Horns until 1954, crafting the magazine to contain a "balanced ration of sense and nonsense": featuring news articles, verse, humor, and poetry intended for "simple cow country folk." An ardent rodeo fan, Mrs. Hopkins came to meet, befriend, and correspond with many rodeo personalities and contestants while promoting and seeking submissions and advertisements for her publication.
Organization
The collection is divided into two series: Correspondence Files and Photographs and Prints. The Correspondence Series is divided into six subseries. The Photographs and Prints Series is divided into three subseries. The contents of each series and subsequent subseries are arranged alphabetically. In many cases original folder titles were retained.
Series I: Correspondence, 1933-1948
Subseries:Advertising Files, 1938-1948
Subseries:Circulation Files, 1935-1948
Subseries:General Files, 1934-1948
Subseries:Performers, 1936-1948
Subseries:Rodeo Files, 1933-1948
Subseries:Submission Files, 1933-1948
Series II: Photographs and Prints, 1936-1954
Subseries:Photographs, 1936-1954
Subseries:Prints, undated
Subseries:Oversized Materials, 1939-1950
Scope and Content Note
Papers, 1933-1948. This collection is composed of the papers of Ethel "Ma" Hopkins. Primarily containing correspondence and her photograph collection amassed during her tenure as editor and publisher of Hoofs and Horns Magazine. Ethel Hopkins' correspondence includes letters discussing rodeo events, advertising, rodeo performers, magazine submissions of all kinds, and magazine subscriptions and circulation. Ethel Hopkins maintained close relationships with many Western writers and rodeo personalities, and there is a personal element throughout much of her correspondence. The General Series includes correspondence documenting daily life in Tucson, the social climate created by World War II, the changing Western landscape, and various accounts of the trials and tribulations of cowboys, ranchers, and rodeo folk. Similarly the photographs and prints contained in the collection include materials gathered for publication in Hoofs and Horns, as well as items inscribed to Mrs. Hopkins personally, illustrating her relationship with specific rodeo characters.
Materials Cataloged Separately
Four monographs from the collection were cataloged separately. They are as follows and can be accessed through the University of Arizona Library Catalog.
Songs of the Southwest, by Juanita Elliott
Autumn Leaves, by May Stevens Isaacs
Left Handed Law, by Charles M. Martin
Rodeo Cowboy, by Charles M. Martin
Access Terms
American periodicals -- History -- 20th century
Hoofs and Horns Magazine -- Records and correspondence
Rodeo performers -- United States
Rodeos -- United States -- History
Women in Rodeos
World War, 1939-1945 -- Arizona -- Tucson
Photographs
Container List
- Correspondence Files, 1933-1948
  7.25 Linear Feet (Approximately 10,875 items)
  Arrangement: Alphabetical
  The Correspondence Files Series is divided into six subseries.
  Advertising Files (1934-1948) contain correspondence regarding prospective and ongoing advertising in Hoofs and Horns Magazine. The letterhead and business workings of various industries that advertised in Hoofs and Horns--notably livestock production and western apparel manufacturing--are represented here. Also included is correspondence regarding classified advertisements of all varieties, appealing to individuals in the rodeo community. Note, some advertising correspondence is attributed to Hoofs and Horns office staff: William Sheldon, Virginia Smith, and Dorothy Bell.
  Circulation Files (1935-1948) is comprised of correspondence regarding the circulation of Hoofs and Horns, including subscriptions, payments, "boost letters" -applauding aspects of Hoofs and Horns, specific copy requests, and copy exchange agreements with other serial publications.
  General Files (1934-1948) contain general inquiries and correspondence relating to the sport of rodeo but not specifically with the publication of Hoofs and Horns. Including correspondence (arranged alphabetically by individual) discussing rodeo, Western life, and personal affairs, and correspondence documenting the assorted inquiries sent to Mrs. Hopkins by readers, organized by subject matter.
  Performers (1936-1948) contain correspondence to and from rodeo performers--announcers, clowns, trick riders and ropers--including several programs and photo representations depicting specific acts of the time.
  Rodeo Files (1933-1948) contain correspondence and announcements between Mrs. Hopkins and rodeo producers and local rodeo associations regarding rodeo events. Rodeo files are arranged alphabetically by the city in which they occurred, with the exception of three "General" files with correspondence regarding rodeo dates, rules, and results that are not attributed to one specific city. Of note in the Rodeo Files are the many colorful, detailed rodeo programs and "Western" stationary elements present in the correspondence. Also included in the Rodeo Files is Mrs. Hopkins' extensive correspondence with the Rodeo Association of America, of which Hoofs and Horns was the official publication.
  Submission Files (1933-1948) contain correspondence regarding material submitted to Hoofs and Horns: stories, poems, photographs, illustrations, news items, corrections, and announcements.
  - Subseries:Advertising Files
    - Classified Advertisements. 1938-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - General. 1936-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Liquor--Acme Beer and Ale. 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Liquor--Blatz Brewing Company. 1934-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Liquor--General. 1934-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Livestock--Armour and Company. 1934-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Livestock--Barmby, Bob. 1939-1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Livestock--Beutler Brothers. 1938-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Livestock--Bradford, Bill. 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Livestock--Burrell, Cuff. 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Livestock--Case, J. L. 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Livestock--Christensen Brothers. 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Livestock--Cooper, Hall. 1941-1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Livestock--Creed, "Shorty" L. U. 1940-1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Livestock--Fisher Palomino Farms. 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Livestock--Gene Autry and Associates. 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Livestock--General. 1937-1948 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Livestock--International Livestock Exposition. 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Livestock--Jory, Ben. 1938-1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Livestock--King, Ray. 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Livestock--Magann, C. C. 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Livestock--Pasco, Luke. 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Livestock--Ritcher, R. A. 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Livestock--Selby, Amos. 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Livestock--Smith-Mahoney Cattle. 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Manufacturers--Chapstick Company. 1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Manufacturers--Dow Chemical Company. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Manufacturers--General. 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Manufacturers--Grey Welding and Trailer Works. 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Manufacturers--Johnson Ideal Halter Co. 1942-1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Manufacturers--J. M. Cattoor and Sons. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Manufacturers--O. M. Franklin Serum Co. 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Manufacturers--Perforated Pad Co. 1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Manufacturers--President Novelty and Jewelry. 1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Manufacturers--Roberts Livestock Spray Co. 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Manufacturers--S. B. Kitchel. 1939-1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Manufacturers--Table Top Rodeo Game. 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Political. 1940-1944 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Publications--Bit and Spur. 1940-1945 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Publications--Cattleman. 1941-1944 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Publications--Desert Magazine. 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Publications--Horse and Mule Association. 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Publications--Macmillan Co. 1947 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Publications--National Charro Association. 1947 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Publications--New Mexico Stockman. 1939-1947 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Publications--Ranch Romances. 1936-1941 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Publications--Texas Livestock Journal. 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Publications--Westermeier, Clifford. 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Publications--Western Horseman. 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Railroads--Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. 1934-1937 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Railroads--Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Co. 1935-1938 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Railroads--General. 1935-1943 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Railroads--Southern Pacific. 1935-1943 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Railroads--Union Pacific Railroad. 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Real Estate--General. 1938-1945 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Real Estate--Palmer House. 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Real Estate--W. F. McIlvain. 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Retail--Montgomery Ward. 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Services--General. 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Services--Harry Roe Co. 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Services--Nix, Loyd. 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Services--Warren Decorating Co. 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Solicitations 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - Taxidermists--Bertilllion, L.D. 1938-1946 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Taxidermists--Jones, Gilbert. 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Taxidermists--Nowotny, M. 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Tobacco--American Tobacco Co. 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Tobacco--B. F. Choate. 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Tobacco--Brown and Williamson Tobacco. 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Tobacco--General. 1935-1942 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Tobacco--Philip Morris and Co. 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Tobacco--Tobacco By-Products and Chemical. 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Western Wear--Baughman's. 1939-1944 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Western Wear--Ben the Rodeo Tailor. 1939-1944 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Western Wear--Carson, Buss. 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Western Wear--Dickey, E.M. 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Western Wear--General. 1941-1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Western Wear--Globe Tailors. 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Western Wear--Hamley and Co. 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Western Wear--H.D. Lee and Co. 1940-1947 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
    - Western Wear--Laredo Hat Co. 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Western Wear--Levi Strauss. 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Western Wear--Mundy, Irby. 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Western Wear--Newell's Cowboy Store. 1939-1947 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Western Wear--Porter's. 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Western Wear--Ray, Allen F. 1943-1948 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Western Wear--Texas Harvest Hat Co. 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Western Wear--Trego's Western Girl 1938-1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Western Wear--Ward, Fay. 1939-1946 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Western Wear--Western Art Leather Co. 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Western Wear--Willig, William. 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Subseries:Circulation Files
    - Boost Letters. 1935-1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Copy Requests. 1933-1948 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Publication Exchanges. 1938-1947 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Subscriptions. 1935-1948 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
    - Subscriptions. 1935-1948 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries:General Files
    - A-F, Miscellaneous. 1938-1949 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - American Saddle and Driving Club. 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Austin, Tex. 1945 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Australian Rough Riders Association. 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Bessler, Joseph. 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Chippendale, Mildred. 1943-1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Crosse, Tex. 1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Slim. 1946 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Elliot, Juanita. 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Forrest, Smokey. 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - G-L, Miscellaneous. 1935-1947 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hammerschmidt, Helen. 1944-1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries--Addresses. 1937-1947 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries--Employment. 1937-1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries--Lodging/Housing. 1936-1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - King, Mat. 1942-1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lauber, Joan. 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - M-P, Miscellaneous. 1937-1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - McBride, Vera. 1943-1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Nick Harris Finance Exchange. 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Palmer, Walter. 1946 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Perry, Reba. 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Pillow, Bob. 1933-1938 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - R-S, Miscellaneous. 1937-1947 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Rendlen, Jean. 1936 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Ross, E. A. 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Sanderson, Irene. 1934-1936 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Scott, Willis. 1934-1938 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Shaw, Richard. 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Shivley, Tex. 1945-1947 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Snook, E. E. 1934 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Society for Crippled Children. 1943-1946 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Stanley, Benoin. 1934-1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Stevens, Harry. 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Stubblefield, Aubrey. 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - T-Z, Miscellaneous. 1935-1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Taillon, Cy. 1945-1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Truehart, Billy. 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Wallin', Shorty. 1944-1947 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Wilkinson, Ella. 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Frederic Allen. 1947 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Wright, Cecil. 1944-1947 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Subseries:Performers
    - Announcers--Bentley, "Bud". 1944-1947 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Announcers--Denslow, Ed. 1947 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Announcers--General. 1941-1947 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Announcers--Hazen, Jimmie. 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Announcers--Holland, Blair. 1946 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Announcers--Irby, E. W. 1947 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Announcers--Jordan, John. 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Announcers--Klein, Geo. 1945-1947 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Announcers--Logan, Pete. 1945-1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Announcers--Normand, Hobart. 1943-1948 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Announcers--Oakey, Jack. 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Announcers--Payne, Gene. 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Announcers--Schrade, Jack. 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Clowns--Bowery, Fred. 1945-1948 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Clowns--Dickson, Jimmy. 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Clowns--General. 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Clowns--Hill, Bobbi. 1939-1946 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Clowns--O'Neil, Harold and Howard. 1943-1948 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Clowns--Reynolds, Fees. 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Clowns--Slim, Dakota. 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Clowns--Sublett, Red. 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous--Allen, Ted. 1938-1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous--Andrews, Jack. 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous--General. 1944-1948 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Trick Riders--Bragg, Nancy. 1940-1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Trick Riders--Carson, Buss. 1947 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Trick Riders--Elder, Jack. 1938 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Trick Riders--General. 1939-1946 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Trick Riders--Griffith, Dick. 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Trick Riders--Guskey Family. 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Trick Riders--Hendricks, Byron. 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Trick Riders--Henry, Pat. 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Trick Riders--Howell, Chet and Juanita. 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Trick Riders--Jernigan, Vance. 1944-1947 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Trick Riders--Lamb, Ted and Betty. 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Trick Riders--Lewis, Kay. 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Trick Riders--McLennan, Don and Hope. 1946 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Trick Riders--Montana, Montie. 1943-1946 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Trick Riders--Pickard, Dick and Pauline. 1940-1948 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Trick Riders--Rex, Harvey. 1947 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Trick Riders--Rivers, Jonnie. 1945-1948 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Trick Riders--Swanson, "Lefty" 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Trick Riders--Walker, George. 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Trick Ropers--Braun, Sylvester. 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Trick Ropers--Dean, Bernice and Frank. 1943-1947 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Trick Ropers--Doss, Jimmie. 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Trick Ropers--General. 1940-1947 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Trick Ropers--Groves, Jimmie. 1946 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Trick Ropers--Seward, Roy. 1943-1948 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Subseries:Rodeo Files
    - Alden (Kansas). 1943-1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ardmore (Oklahoma). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Baker (Montana). 1938 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Bakersfield (California). 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Belle Fourche (South Dakota). 1934-1938 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Benson (Arizona). 1935-1938 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Big Spring (Texas). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Blackfoot (Idaho). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Blythe (California). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Boise (Idaho). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Boston (Massachusetts). 1934-1937 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Buffalo (Oklahoma). 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Burwell (Nebraska). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Butte (Montana). 1935-1939 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Caldwell (Idaho). 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Calgary (Alberta, Canada). 1935-1938 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Canadian (Texas). 1933-1938 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Cardston (Alberta, Canada). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Carlsbad (New Mexico). 1936, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Casa Grande (Arizona). 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Chandler (Arizona). 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Colorado Springs (Colorado). 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Darmstadt (Germany). 1946 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Dinuba (California). 1936 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Durango (Colorado). 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Ekalaka (Montana). 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - El Paso (Texas). 1933, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ennis (Montana). 1938 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Evanston (Wyoming). 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Filler (Idaho). 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Florence (Arizona). 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Fort Worth (Texas). 1935-1937 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Gatesville (Texas). 1938 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - General--Dates. 1935-1947 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - General--Inquiries. 1938-1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - General--Results. 1944-1948 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Gillette (Wyoming). 1938 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Gilroy (California). 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Gooding (Idaho). 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Great Falls (Montana). 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Hanford (California). 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Hinton (Oklahoma). 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hollister (California). 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Houston (Texas). 1938 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Huntsville (Texas). 1939 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Idaho Falls (Idaho). 1937 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - King City (California). 1937 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Kingman (Arizona). 1936-1938 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Lakeside (California). 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Lakeview (Oregon). 1935-1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Las Vegas (New Mexico). 1947 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Las Vegas (Nevada). 1936 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Lewiston (Montana). 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Little Rock (Arkansas). 1938 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Livermore (California). 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Livingston (Montana). 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Los Angeles (California). 1937-1944 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Magnum (Oklahoma). 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Marysville (California). 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Medicine Hat (Alberta, Canada). 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Memphis (Tennessee). 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Midland (Texas). 1938 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Minot (North Dakota). 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Monte Vista (Colorado). 1934-1938 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Montrose (California). 1934, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Nampa (Idaho). 1935-1938 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Nephi (Utah). 1936 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - New York (New York). 1934-1938 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - North Platte (Nebraska). 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Oakland (Nebraska). 1936 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Ogden (Utah). 1935-1938 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Oklahoma City (Oklahoma). 1935-1937 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Olton (Texas). 1938 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pecos (Texas). 1938 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Pendleton (Oregon). 1937-1947 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Palatka (Florida). 1948 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Phillipsburg (Kansas). 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Phoenix (Arizona). 1936-1938 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Pocatello (Idaho). 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Porterville (California). 1938 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Pueblo (Colorado). 1936-1938 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Red Bluff (California). 1935-1938 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Red Lodge (Montana). 1935-1938 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Redondo Beach (California). 1938 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Reno (Nevada). 1936-1938 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Riggins (Idaho). 1947 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Rochester (New York). 1936-1938 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Rodeo Association of America. 1933-1945 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
    - Rodeo Association of America. 1933-1945 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Sacramento (California). 1938 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Salinas (California). 1947 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Salt Lake City (Utah). 1936-1938 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - San Angelo (Texas). 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - San Antonio (Texas). 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - San Jacinto (California). 1938 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sanderson (Texas). 1937 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Seattle (Washington). 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Sheridan (Wyoming). 1934-1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Sidney (Iowa). 1935-1937 (Box 13, Folder 11)